icccricketstore.com 2016-05-21

# Privacy Policy

### Table of Contents:

  1. Respecting your privacy
  2. What kinds of personal information do we collect and hold?
  3. How do we collect and hold personal information?
  4. Why do we collect, hold, use and disclose personal information?
  5. How can you enquire about, access and correct your personal information?
  6. How can you complain about our management of personal information?
  7. Our sharing of your personal information overseas
  8. Updates
  9. Other privacy terms and limits of this policy
  10. Cookies Statement
  11. Credit Card Security

### 1\. Respecting your privacy

The ICC Official Online Shop is operated by Gaames Unlimited under license from Velocity Brand Management. We are committed to protecting your privacy, and to compliance with applicable privacy laws which set out standards for the management of personal information. This policy outlines our personal information management practices. Specifically:

  * the kinds of personal information we collect and hold;
  * how we collect and hold it;
  * the purposes for which we collect, hold, use and disclose it;
  * your right to access and seek correction of it;
  * how you may complain about privacy matters; and
  * our sharing of your personal information overseas.

There are some matters to which this policy does not apply. These are referred to in clause 9 below.

### 2\. What kinds of personal information do we collect and hold?

We collect and hold personal information that is reasonably necessary for the operation of the ICC Official Online Shop, which may include:

  * your personal details such as your name, email and/or physical addresses, telephone numbers, employer, date of birth, age and gender;
  * financial information (such as your credit card details);
  * your order number, customer reference number or loyalty card number;
  * any rewards and redemption details applicable to your membership of one of our loyalty programs;
  * what, how and when you buy from us or have expressed an interest in buying from us; and
  * demographic information such as your postcode and your stated or likely preferences, for example whether you may be interested in particular products or promotions.

You generally have the option of not identifying yourself or of using a pseudonym when dealing with us, but not where this is impractical (for example when you shop online with us) or where the law or a court order provides otherwise.

### 3\. How do we collect and hold personal information?

_Collection of personal information:_

When we collect personal information about you, we do so by making a record of it. We do this when:

  * you visit our websites;
  * you purchase products from us online;
  * you register with us, for example to create an account, to become a member of one of our loyalty programs or to send you information;
  * you communicate with us online;
  * you take part in our promotions, competitions, testimonials, surveys and focus groups;
  * you deal with us in other ways involving a need for personal information to be provided such as when you contact one of our call centres or chat lines or bring a claim against us.

We may also collect personal information about you by accessing data from other sources and then analysing that data together with the information we already hold about you in order to learn more about your likely preferences and interests. When you visit our websites, social media pages or mobile applications or click on our advertisements on online media, we may collect information about you using technology which is not apparent to you, for example “cookies“. For information about our use of this technology, refer to the Cookies Statement at end of policy.

Most of the personal information we collect and hold about you is from your direct dealings with us, but there are some instances where we may collect your personal information other than from you directly. For example from other suppliers who, in common with us, have a relationship with you, or on whose behalf we process your purchases.

_Holding of personal information:_

Personal information we hold is stored on our web servers in secure environments. These servers may be operated by us or by our service providers. In all cases, we have rigorous information security requirements aimed at eliminating risks of unauthorised access to, and loss, misuse or wrongful alteration of, personal information.

All credit/debit card information you provide to us is transmitted via secure technology to the payment processor. Credit card details are not stored by us. For more information about credit card security, refer to the Credit Card Security at end of policy.

Your personal information is password-protected to prevent unauthorised access to it. You should not divulge your password to anyone.

### 4\. Why do we collect, hold, use and disclose personal information?

When we collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information, we do so primarily to sell and promote our products and services to you and to improve on the range of our offerings. For example:

  * to learn of your likely preferences so that we may promote our products and services to you in a way which may be of most interest to you; and
  * to assist in investigating your complaints and enquiries.

We disclose personal information we collect for purposes which are incidental to the sale and promotion of our products and services to you. For example, we may disclose your personal information within our group, to service providers who assist us in our day-to-day business operations and as part of buying or selling businesses.

We may collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information for other purposes which are within reasonable expectations or where permitted by law. When marketing to you, your personal information is only ever used or disclosed for our own purposes or those of our group companies. You may opt out of our direct marketing to you at any time. Our direct marketing materials will tell you how to do this.

We may de-identify your personal information. We may do this for use and disclosure of the anonymous data to determine preferences and shopping patterns.

### 5\. How can you enquire about, access and correct your personal information?

_Enquiry and access:_

We will provide you with access to any of your personal information we hold (except in limited circumstances recognised by law). If you wish to access your personal information or have an enquiry about privacy, please contact our Privacy Officer at: [privacy@vbmglobal.com](mailto:privacy@vbmglobal.com) or by calling us on +918065690377.

Alternatively, you can write to us at:

Privacy Officer   
Gaames Unlimited   
#201, 10th 'D' Main, 1st Block, Jayanagar   
Bengaluru 560011

Before we provide you with access to your personal information we may require some proof of identity. We may charge a reasonable fee for giving access to your personal information if your request requires substantial effort on our part.

_Correction:_

If you need to correct your personal information, please contact our Privacy Officer at one of the above contact points.

### 6\. How can you complain about our management of personal information?

If you wish to complain about a breach of the privacy rules that bind us, you may contact our Privacy Officer at one of the above contact points. We may ask you to put your complaint in writing and to provide details about it. We may discuss your complaint with our personnel and our service providers and others as appropriate.

Our Privacy Officer will investigate the matter and attempt to resolve it in a timely way. Our Privacy Officer will inform you in writing about the outcome of the investigation. 

### 7\. Our sharing of your personal information overseas

It is our policy to require all of our overseas sharing of personal information to be done in a way which requires observance of strict privacy and security standards, both during transit and at the overseas destination. We may allow your personal information to be shared with those who are in countries other than your own location. We do this:

  * where we have made a business decision to host our websites or store our data with trusted service providers who are in the business of providing website hosting, data storage and/or data processing services. These services commonly involve diverse geographic locations which change from time to time for reasons which include data protection and processing efficiency. Where these services are used by us, it is not practical for us to notify you of which country your personal information may be located in; and
  * for disclosures between our group companies. Our main business location is in India and Velocity Brand Management's is Australia, but some of our respective group companies may be based in other countries from time to time;
  * when our business which collected your personal information is in a different country to your location;
  * when our supply to you necessarily involves overseas disclosures. For example where we need to provide certain of your personal information to one or more of our overseas product suppliers in order to fulfil your order;
  * where you are involved with public liability issues concerning a product we may disclose your personal information to any overseas supplier of such a product in the course of managing those issues.

### 8\. Updates

This privacy policy is current as of the date below. We may change it from time to time. If we do change it we will publish the updated version on ICC Official Online Shop from which point the updated version will apply.

### 9\. Other privacy terms and limits of this policy

This is a policy. There may be additional privacy notices and terms relevant to you depending on the nature of your dealings with us and on our particular businesses. For example we may have different or additional privacy terms governing our loyalty programs, or on our corporate website [www.gaamesunlimited.com](http://www.gaamesunlimited.com/), and we have separate charters concerning the personal information of our employees. There are also separate terms governing the use of our sites and the purchase of products from our sites.

### Cookies Statement:

_About this statement_

This statement gives you information about our use of cookies. This is relevant to when you use your computer or mobile device to visit online content (such as websites and mobile apps) which display or promote us or our products and services. The content may be our own, or may be the content of others in which we have an interest, such as our banner advertisements.

Cookies may be arranged (“set”) by us or by others under an arrangement with us, such as companies whose business it is to analyse information. We may also access information from cookies set by others (“3rd party cookies”).

_Why should you know about cookies?_

You should know about cookies because they involve the collection of information about you (which may or may not be personal information) in a way which may not be obvious to you.

_What is a cookie?_

Cookies are small pieces of information captured when your device is used to access online content. Cookies are stored in your device by the person who arranges for the cookie to be set. This person may be the provider of the content being accessed, or it might be a 3rd party. 3rd party cookies are used to provide information about your device's access to more than one discrete site or data set.

_Why do we allow cookies to be used?_

We allow cookies to be used for three reasons.

  * First, we allow session cookies to be used when you visit our online content. This enables your device to move from page to page without having to log in repeatedly. These generally improve your browsing experience.
  * Second, we allow persistent (permanent) cookies to be used to better inform how the content your device visits may be presented to you. Persistent cookies can store your preferences for a particular site, so they will be remembered when the site is visited again.
  * Third, we allow persistent and other kinds of permanent cookies (such as “flash” cookies) to be set and we access information from 3rd party cookies in order to assist in compiling and analysing the types of online content you visit and your interaction with that content. This assists us to assess what promotions to offer to you, and when and how. It also assists us to measure the effectiveness of our promotions.

_What are your choices about cookies?_

You can control the extent to which your device allows cookies to be set on it. You can do this by changing the settings on the software your device uses to access the internet (your browser software). For example, depending on which browser your device uses, you may be able to disable third party cookies.

There is a lot of information available about how cookies work and how to change your browser’s cookie preferences. This includes information at the following link:

### Credit Card Security:

We take the utmost precautions to protect your credit card details.

When your credit card details are submitted via the website, that information is encrypted and transmitted to the payment processors (typically PayPal, PayU, Payflow and/or banks) by industry standard 128bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology equivalent to that used by Banks for online banking transactions. This ensures that if anyone else on the Internet is somehow able to intercept the communication he/she will only be able to see it in an encrypted (garbled) form. SSL Certificate technology allows our payment processors to decrypt the information, and view it in plain text form for processing.

We and our service providers adopt systems and procedures designed to detect the fraudulent use of credit cards. It is possible that we or our service providers may contact you requiring additional verification of your credit card details as part of these systems and procedures. If, however, you have any doubt as to the legitimacy of any such contact or request, or indeed any other questions regarding our handling of your credit card information, please do not hesitate to contact us at [privacy@vbmglobal.com](mailto:privacy@vbmglobal.com) or +918065690377 before actioning any such request.
